Hoang Van Nam

Back-end Developer

→ +035 776 3553
namnam290703@gmail.com
Ha Noi

CAREER GOALS

Apply the knowledge you have learned into practice, experience challenges at work and work with your passion. Develop and improve your programming skills to become a professional programmer. Desire to work in a dynamic, creative environment, with opportunities to learn and develop professionally.

During your internship, try to accumulate knowledge and skills and develop into an official employee position. And 2 years later, I became a leader, leading the next generation to develop themselves and consolidate the company's development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Database: SqlSever, MySql.
- Backend: C#, PHP, Java, JavaScript, .NET.
- Frontend: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Windows Forms.
- Framework: Entity Framework.

EDUCATION

HANOI COLLEGE OF INDUSTRIAL ECONOMICS (Vietnam)

06/2021 - 06/2024

- Learn about software and websites
- GPA 3.6

WORK EXPERIENCE

HANOI COLLEGE OF INDUSTRIAL ECONOMICS

09/2021 - 06/2024

Human resource management system

- Position: Programmer
- Number of members: 1 person.
- Job Description: Building a human resources management system for a pharmaceutical company, using Visual Studio tool to create WindowsForm interface, code other functions of the system.
- Technology used: Windows Form, C#, SqlSever.
- Result :
- Build human resource management system software.
- The project was evaluated well by the examination board.

NACENCOMM card technology company

02/2024 - 05/2024

Build a sales website

- Position: Programmer
- Number of members: 1 person.
- Job Description: Build a sales website using Visual Studio tools to create the website interface and code other system functions.
- Technology used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, C#, Asp.Net MVC
- Result:

- Successfully built sales website interface.
- Respond well to customer feedback requests.

FINATECH 05/2024 - 06/2024

Write API for function operations

- Position: Programmer
- Number of members: 2 persons.
- Job Description: Create APIs for adding, editing, deleting, and updating features, write a statement to query data from the database using procedure.
- Technology used: C#, Web APi.
- Result:
- Features work well.
- Respond well to customer feedback requests.

SODI MEDIA 06/2024 -

Build websites with open source code

- Position: Programmer
- Number of members: 1 persons.
- Job Description: Web design with open source WordPress according to customer requirements. Analyze system design and understand and take care of customer needs.
- Technology used: Wordpress, Php, Mysql.
- Result:
- Design beautiful, successful websites with open source code as required.
- Received high praise from customer and team feedback on designed products.

CERTIFICATE

• English certificate: B1.

PARTICIPATING PROJECTS

Human resource management of ECO company

(12/2023 - 1/2024)

Customer	Employee
Description	Software to manage all human resources issues for ECO pharmaceutical company
Number of members	1
Position	FrontEnd Developer,BackEnd Developer
Role	-Review design -Setup environment -Code interface(Windows Form) and function(for the user interacts with the software) -Fulfill requests for feedback from users -Fix bugs
Technology	.NET Framework, C#,SQL Sever

Shoe store

(02/2024 - 5/2024)

Customer	Client

Description	Website provides shoe products to customers
Number of members	1
Position	FrontEnd Developer,BackEnd Developer
Role	-System design analysis -Website design using html, css,bootstrap,javascrip -Using Asp.NET technology on the website with the MVC model coded in C# language to retrieve data information from customers -Stores data and information in SQL Server database -Fulfill requests for feedback from users
Technology	.NET Framework, C#, SQL Sever, Entity Framework, Html, Css, Bootstrap, Js.

HOBBIES

- Read stories
- Listen to music
- Gaming

© topcv.vn